Anupam Singh (1) Featured

MCA with more than three years experience in PHP Developer, Website Development, Bootstrap, CSS3, HTML5, MySQL, Javascript, Jquery, PHP core, wordpress, codeigniter, Laravel



Current Designation: PHP Developer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Current Company: Bow Advertising Pvt Ltd Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Noida Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Delhi / NCR, Noida, Delhi

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: php developer, mysql, responsive web design, website developer, wordpress, shopify,laravel,php developer,

mysql, html5, css, bootstrap, responsive web design,codeigniter

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Nov-20 Last Modified: 19-Nov-20

Summary

I have 4 years experience in Web & Mobile Application Development as PHP Developer. I am using Framework as Laravel, CI & REST API too with MYSQL DB. I have keen desire to work with similar platform in a reputed Web & Mobile App Development company.

Work Experience

Bow Advertising Pvt Ltd as PHP Developer

May 2020 to Till Date

Working on a product as a mobile application "SHOUT CAMPUS", role to prepare backend panel & REST API.

Ajath Infotech Pvt. Ltd. as PHP Developer

Apr 2019 to Apr 2020

Working as PHP Developer using Codeigniter & Laravel with MYSQL, REST API

ENS Enterprises Pvt. Ltd as PHP Developer

Nov 2017 to Mar 2019

Software Engineer Grade II

WEB SEEKERS as PHP Developer

Jul 2016 to Oct 2017

Fresher & Jr. PHP Developer

Education

UG: BCA (Computers), Correspondence/Distance Learning from Motilal Nehru National Institute of Technology in 2011

PG: MCA (Computers), Correspondence/Distance Learning from MOTILAL NEHRU NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF **TECHNOLOGY** in 2013

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version | Last Used | Experience |
|-----------------------|---------|-----------|----------------------|
| HTML5 | | 2018 | 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| css3 | | 2018 | 2 Year(s) 6 Month(s) |
| php core | | 2020 | 2 Year(s) 8 Month(s) |
| MY SQL | | 2020 | 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| WORDPRESS | | 2018 | 1 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| codelgniter Framework | | 2019 | 1 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| Laravel | | 2020 | 1 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | Expert | | | |
| Hindi | Expert | | | |

Projects

Project Title: sargammishra Client: Sargam Mishra

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2016 - Jun 2016 Project Location: sargammishra.com Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 1

Skill Used: PHP & MYSQL

Role Description: Worked on coding as well as design too.

Project Details: A website for healing and yoga with payment gatway

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Countries: India

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time